{"title": ["Verb to be: questions and negatives", "Short answers ", "Prepositions", "Possessive\u2018s ", "Opposite adjectives", "The family ", "Food and drink"], "count": 57, "Question0": {"question": "\u201c_____ her name Eliza?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) What / it isn\u2019t ", "B) Is / she isn\u2019t", "C) Is / it is not ", "D) Is / it isn\u2019t"], "answer": "D"}, "Question1": {"question": "Is your surname Anderson?", "example": ["A) Yes, you are. ", "B) Yes, it is.", "C) Yes, I am. ", "D) Yes, my is."], "answer": "B"}, "Question2": {"question": "\u201cIs she American?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) hers isn\u2019t ", "B) she isn\u2019t ", "C) she is not ", "D) she her isn\u2019t"], "answer": "B"}, "Question3": {"question": "\u201c____ their names Jack & Benny?\u201d / \u201cYes, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) Are / they are ", "B) Aren\u2019t / there are", "C) Am / their ", "D) Is / they\u2019re"], "answer": "A"}, "Question4": {"question": "\u201cIs your dog 2 years old?\u201d / \u201cYes, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) it\u2019s ", "B) dog is ", "C) it is ", "D) its"], "answer": "C"}, "Question5": {"question": "\u201cIs your elder brother married?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) brother isn\u2019t ", "B) he isn\u2019t", "C) he is not ", "D) she isn\u2019t"], "answer": "B"}, "Question6": {"question": "\u201cAre you from Senegal?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) I\u2019m not ", "B) I amn\u2019t ", "C) I are not ", "D) I not"], "answer": "A"}, "Question7": {"question": "\u201c_____ Martha English?\u201d / \u201cYes, she _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) Is / isn\u2019t ", "B) Are / is ", "C) Is / is ", "D) Are / is"], "answer": "C"}, "Question8": {"question": "\u201c_____ her surname Smith?\u201d / \u201cNo, it _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) What / isn\u2019t ", "B) Is / is ", "C) Is / isn\u2019t ", "D) Are / isn\u2019t"], "answer": "C"}, "Question9": {"question": "\u201cAre you a student?\u201d / \u201cYes, I _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) am ", "B) have ", "C) is ", "D) \u2018m not"], "answer": "A"}, "Question10": {"question": "\u201c_____ you from Barcelona?\u201d / \u201cNo, I\u2019m not.\u201d", "example": ["A) Is ", "B) Are ", "C) Do ", "D) Where"], "answer": "B"}, "Question11": {"question": "\u201c_____ you married?\u201d / \u201cNo, I _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) Aren\u2019t / am ", "B) Are / am", "C) Is / am not ", "D) Are / \u2019m not"], "answer": "D"}, "Question12": {"question": "\u201c_____ is Brenda?\u201d / \u201cShe\u2019s Patrick\u2019s wife.\u201d", "example": ["A) What ", "B) Who ", "C) Which ", "D) Where"], "answer": "B"}, "Question13": {"question": "My teacher\u2019s name _____ John.", "example": ["A) are ", "B) is ", "C) am ", "D) not"], "answer": "B"}, "Question14": {"question": "Marcus and Carlos _____ my brothers.", "example": ["A) is ", "B) am ", "C) are ", "D) be"], "answer": "C"}, "Question15": {"question": "My mother and father _____ at work.", "example": ["A) is ", "B) am ", "C) are ", "D) *"], "answer": "C"}, "Question16": {"question": "It _____ Monday today.", "example": ["A) is ", "B) am ", "C) are ", "D) *"], "answer": "A"}, "Question17": {"question": "This is the photo _____ my family.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) at ", "C) of ", "D) on"], "answer": "C"}, "Question18": {"question": "It\u2019s good practice _____ you.", "example": ["A) for ", "B) at ", "C) of ", "D) in"], "answer": "A"}, "Question19": {"question": "I\u2019m _____ home.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) on ", "C) at ", "D) from"], "answer": "C"}, "Question20": {"question": "I\u2019m _____ La Guardia Community College.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) on ", "C) at ", "D) of"], "answer": "C"}, "Question21": {"question": "I\u2019m _____ New York.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) for ", "C) at ", "D) of"], "answer": "A"}, "Question22": {"question": "I\u2019m _____ a class _____ eight other students.", "example": ["A) in / for ", "B) at / of ", "C) in / with ", "D) at / off"], "answer": "C"}, "Question23": {"question": "I live _____ an apartment _____ two American boys.", "example": ["A) in / of ", "B) at / with ", "C) in / with ", "D) of/with"], "answer": "C"}, "Question24": {"question": "Central Park is lovely _____ the snow.", "example": ["A) at ", "B) in ", "C) of ", "D) with"], "answer": "B"}, "Question25": {"question": "\u201c_____ is his job?\u201d / \u201cHe _____ a policeman.\u201d", "example": ["A) Which / is ", "B) What / are ", "C) What / is ", "D) Where / is"], "answer": "C"}, "Question26": {"question": "He _____ from Argentina. He is _____ Mexico.", "example": ["A) is / from ", "B) isn\u2019t / from ", "C) isn\u2019t / in ", "D) aren\u2019t / in"], "answer": "B"}, "Question27": {"question": "\u201c_____ _____ is a hamburger and chips?\u201d / \u201cThree pounds fifty.\u201d", "example": ["A) How many ", "B) How often ", "C) How much ", "D) How long"], "answer": "C"}, "Question28": {"question": "~ 35. Find the opposite word.  =>  easy - ______", "example": ["A) cold ", "B) cheap ", "C) difference ", "D) difficult"], "answer": "D"}, "Question29": {"question": "lovely - ______", "example": ["A) old ", "B) expensive ", "C) horrible ", "D) quick"], "answer": "C"}, "Question30": {"question": "fast - ______", "example": ["A) slow ", "B) small ", "C) quick ", "D) warm"], "answer": "A"}, "Question31": {"question": "expensive - ______", "example": ["A) big ", "B) cheap ", "C) cold ", "D) hot"], "answer": "B"}, "Question32": {"question": "hot - ______", "example": ["A) cold ", "B) new ", "C) warm ", "D) small"], "answer": "A"}, "Question33": {"question": "big - ______", "example": ["A) high ", "B) small ", "C) tall ", "D) slow"], "answer": "B"}, "Question34": {"question": "young - ______", "example": ["A) old ", "B) big ", "C) small ", "D) quick"], "answer": "A"}, "Question35": {"question": "\u201cAre you married?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) I am not ", "B) I\u2019m not ", "C) I amn\u2019t ", "D) I m not"], "answer": "B"}, "Question36": {"question": "Brazil ____ in Asia. ____ in South America.", "example": ["A) is / It isn\u2019t ", "B) is / It\u2019s ", "C) is / Is ", "D) isn\u2019t / It\u2019s"], "answer": "D"}, "Question37": {"question": "Snow is _____ .", "example": ["A) cold ", "B) hot ", "C) small ", "D) cheap"], "answer": "A"}, "Question38": {"question": "A: _____ Greek? / B: Yes, I am.", "example": ["A) You ", "B) Are you ", "C) Am I ", "D) I"], "answer": "B"}, "Question39": {"question": "We _____ in a Russian class. / We _____ in an English class.", "example": ["A) are / are ", "B) are / not ", "C) aren\u2019t / are ", "D) are / am"], "answer": "C"}, "Question40": {"question": "Rolls-Royce cars are _____ .", "example": ["A) cheap ", "B) blue ", "C) expensive ", "D) tall"], "answer": "C"}, "Question41": {"question": "\u201c_____ your teachers married?\u201d / \u201cYes, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) Is / he is ", "B) Is / he\u2019s ", "C) Is / she is ", "D) Are / they are"], "answer": "D"}, "Question42": {"question": "\u201cIs it hot today?\u201d / \u201cNo, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) it isn\u2019t ", "B) it is not ", "C) it\u2019s not ", "D) it not"], "answer": "A"}, "Question43": {"question": "\u201cAre _____ your parents?\u201d / \u201cYes, _____ .\u201d", "example": ["A) they-their are ", "B) their-they are", "C) they-they are ", "D) they-they"], "answer": "C"}, "Question44": {"question": "Eliza _____ from Greece. _____ from Poland.", "example": ["A) is / Is ", "B) isn\u2019t / She\u2019s ", "C) is / Isn\u2019t ", "D) is / Is not"], "answer": "B"}, "Question45": {"question": "Ann is _____ wife.", "example": ["A) John\u2019s ", "B) John is ", "C) John\u2019s is ", "D) John"], "answer": "A"}, "Question46": {"question": "This is not just my computer. It is 4 _____ computer.", "example": ["A) students\u2019 ", "B) students\u2019s ", "C) student\u2019s ", "D) student"], "answer": "A"}, "Question47": {"question": "A: What is _____ ?", "example": ["A) his job ", "B) she job ", "C) he job ", "D) her job"], "answer": "D"}, "Question48": {"question": "\u201cHow old is your brother?\u201d / \u201c_____ 29.\u201d", "example": ["A) They are ", "B) I am ", "C) It is ", "D) He is"], "answer": "D"}, "Question49": {"question": "\u201cHow old _____ Mr. & Mrs. White?\u201d / \u201c_____ 50 and 48.\u201d", "example": ["A) is / They ", "B) are / They\u2019re", "C) are / They ", "D) */ They are"], "answer": "B"}, "Question50": {"question": "\u201cHow old ___, Andrew?\u201d / \u201c_____ 21 years old.\u201d", "example": ["A) are you / I\u2019m ", "B) is he / He\u2019s", "C) is / He is ", "D) are / I"], "answer": "A"}, "Question51": {"question": "\u201c_____ you now?\u201d / \u201cI\u2019m at the school.\u201d", "example": ["A) Where\u2019s ", "B) Where\u2019re are", "C) Where\u2019re ", "D) Where"], "answer": "C"}, "Question52": {"question": "\u201cWhere _____ now?\u201d / \u201cIn her office.\u201d", "example": ["A) is he ", "B) is she ", "C) is it ", "D) is"], "answer": "B"}, "Question53": {"question": "\u201c_____ is his father\u2019s job?\u201d / \u201cHe\u2019s a teacher.\u201d", "example": ["A) Who ", "B) When ", "C) Why ", "D) What"], "answer": "D"}, "Question54": {"question": "This is those _____ toy.", "example": ["A) kid\u2019s ", "B) kid ", "C) kids\u2019s ", "D) kids\u2019"], "answer": "D"}, "Question55": {"question": "They are not my _____ books.", "example": ["A) children\u2019s ", "B) childs ", "C) children\u2019 ", "D) children of"], "answer": "A"}, "Question56": {"question": "They\u2019re not his _____ mistakes.", "example": ["A) friend\u2019s ", "B) friend ", "C) friends ", "D) friends\u2019"], "answer": "A"}}